Love, Romance & Chocolate is a tv movie, romance
film directed by Jonathan Wright.
Emma and chocolatier Luc compete for Belgium's Royal Chocolatier.
The beauty and romance of Bruges inspire unique chocolate combinations,
but will their entry win without them losing their hearts?
Emma Colvin, played by Lacey Chabert.
Luc Simon, played by Will Kemp.
Marie Gruben, played by Brittany Bristow.
Max Van Dender, played by Guillaume Dolmans.
Frederic, played by Joseph Olivennes.
Annabelle De Meyer, played by Loriane Klupsch.
Romance films involve romantic love stories recorded in visual media for broadcast in theatres or on television
that focus on passion, emotion, and the affectionate romantic involvement of the main characters.
Typically their journey through dating, courtship or marriage is featured.
These films focus on the search for romantic love as the main plot focus.
Occasionally, romance lovers face obstacles such as finances, physical illness, various
forms of discrimination, psychological restraints, or family resistance.
As in all quite strong, deep, and close romantic relationships, the tensions of day-to-day life, temptations
(of infidelity), and differences in compatibility enter into the plots of romantic films.
Romantic films often explore the essential themes of love at first sight, young and mature love, unrequited love, obsession, sentimental love,
spiritual love, forbidden love, platonic love, sexual and passionate love, sacrificial love, explosive and destructive love, and tragic love.
Romantic films serve as great escapes and fantasies for viewers, especially if the two leads finally overcome their
difficulties, declare their love, and experience their "happily ever after", often implied by a reunion and final kiss.
In romantic television series, such romantic relationships may develop over many episodes
or different characters may become intertwined in different romantic arcs.
Screenwriter and scholar Eric R.
Williams identifies Romance Films as one of eleven super-genres in his screenwriters' taxonomy,
claiming that all feature-length narrative films can be classified by these super-genres.
The other ten super-genres are action, crime, fantasy, horror, science
fiction, comedy, sports, thriller, war and western.
The film explores themes of chocolate, belgium,
travel, valentine's day, hallmark.
The tone is emotional.